playdominion.com 2016-06-15

# Privacy Policy | Making Fun, Inc.

**Updated September 5, 2015**

Summary of the Making Fun, Inc. Privacy Policy:

**1\. INTRODUCTION –  **The Introduction identifies the basic Making Fun Services covered by this Privacy Policy and provides a brief overview of what this Privacy Policy covers.

**2\. SUBMISSION AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION –  **This section addresses the types of information that Making Fun collects directly from users and collection of non-personally identifiable information via cookies and related technologies by, and on behalf of, Making Fun and third parties.

**3\. NOTICE –  **This section provides information on how Making Fun notifies users about future Policy changes, where Making Fun stores data, and third-party websites that may link to the Making Fun Services.

**4\. USE AND DISCLOSURE –  **This section describes how Making Fun uses your information to provide and manage the Making Fun Services, including when Making Fun may disclose your information to third parties that assist Making Fun in providing those services.

**5\. SECURITY –  **This section describes Making Fun’s security measures.

**6\. USER CONTROL AND ACCOUNT CANCELLATION –  **This section informs users how to access and change their personal information stored by Making Fun, and how to cancel their accounts.

**7\. CONTACT US –  **This section instructs users how to contact Making Fun.

**1\. INTRODUCTION**

Making Fun, Inc. (“Making Fun” or “we”) is a publisher and developer of mobile and social games. The services Making Fun offers include MakingFun.com, games published on a variety of platforms, and other features, content, games or applications offered, from time to time, by or on behalf of, Making Fun, including when these services are accessed via the Internet, mobile or other device (collectively, the “Making Fun Services”).  Making Fun is based in the United States.

As set forth in our [Terms of Use](http://www.makingfun.com/terms-of-services/), the Making Fun Services are general audience, are not targeted to children, and do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.

This Privacy Policy applies to all users.  This Policy describes the collection and use of users’ personal information on the Making Fun Services. It also describes generally Making Fun’s practices for handling non-personally identifiable information (e.g., interests, demographics and site usage) to the extent such information is associated with a particular user or user account.

**2\. SUBMISSION AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION ON MAKING FUN SERVICES**

_User Submitted Information_

**Third-Party Account Information.  **When you access a Making Fun Service through a third-party connection or log-in, we may collect your user ID and/or user name associated with that third-party service, or any information you have submitted in connection with that service and which the third party shares with partner services.

**Email Address.  **If email address is not included in such information, Making Fun may ask you to submit your email address directly to Making Fun.

**Public Site Content**  consists of information you disclose in public areas of the Making Fun Services, such as forums, message boards, chat rooms, gameplay sessions, and other community areas.  It also includes the information about you that accompanies this content, such as a username or user picture.  Please be aware that Public Site Content is always public and available to everyone and may be displayed in search results both on the Making Fun Services and on external search engines. By way of example, gameplay logs containing usernames, timestamps and gameplay data may be made available over the public internet for players to download and analyze for their enjoyment. Please do not use a username that can identify you personally (for example because you use it on other sites that reveal additional information about you) if you have any concerns about this information being freely available.

**Correspondence**  consists of information you disclose when you contact Making Fun, for example, for customer service purposes.

_Making Fun  Collected Information_

**Making Fun  Site Activity Information. **When users access the Making Fun Services, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about those visits.  For example, in order to permit your connection to the Making Fun Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information.  If you access the Making Fun Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device in order to serve content to it.  We also may use cookies and other tracking technologies (including browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies), which are comprised of small bits of data that often include an anonymous unique identifier.  Websites send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so that Making Fun can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that site.  We may use these technologies to collect and store information about your usage of the Making Fun Services, such as pages you have visited, game sessions you have played, search queries you have run, and advertisements you have seen.

Third parties that support the Making Fun Services by serving advertisements or providing services, such as allowing users to share content or tracking aggregate site usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information.  Making Fun does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies.  For more information about third-party ad networks that use these technologies, see [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether.  Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information.  Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe’s website, see <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html>.  Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features or personalization available through the Making Fun Services.

**Third Parties.  **To improve the quality of the Making Fun Services, we may also supplement the information we collect with information from third parties.

**Not Track.**  Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. At the present time, the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) has not yet established universal standards for recognizable DNT signals, and, therefore, Making Fun, nor it’s publishing or affiliated partners, does not recognize DNT.

**3\. NOTICE & CHOICE**

**Means of Notice.  **This Privacy Policy is the primary means by which Making Fun provides you with notice about its collection and use of your information.

**Privacy Policy Changes.  **Making Fun may modify this Privacy Policy as necessary.  If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy that expand our rights to use your personal information, we will notify you to seek your consent through email or a prominent posting on the site.

**Location of Data.  **The Making Fun Services are mostly hosted in the United States, although some Making Fun Services are hosted in Europe, Asia and South America to improve the speed of serving users in those areas.  If you are a user located outside the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to and processed in the United States.  U.S. data protection and other relevant laws may not be the same as those in your jurisdiction.  As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.

**Linked Websites.  **The Making Fun Services may also be linked to sites or services operated third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes, or applications developed and maintained by third parties. Making Fun is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you submit information directly to a third party, leave the Making Fun Services via a link, enable a third-party service, or click an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of that third-party.

**Collection of Personal Financial Information by a Third Party**.  If you elect to purchase any products or services through Making Fun, you may be required to provide personal financial information, including your credit card information, billing address or other payment information) (collectively, “Personal Financial Information”), full name, phone number and shipping address in order to purchase such product or service. At the time of your purchase, Making Fun will notify you of the identity of any third party that is collecting, transmitting, storing and/or processing your Personal Financial Information.  **You acknowledge and agree that this Privacy Policy will not apply to any Personal Financial Information that you provide to any independent third party company via the  Making Fun Services and that all payment obligations related to such purchase shall be governed solely by the applicable independent third party company’s privacy policy.  You further acknowledge and agree that Making Fun will have no liability for or control over such independent third party company’s use or protection of your Personal Financial Information.** You should check the privacy policy of the independent third party company‘s website to determine how it will handle any Personal Financial Information it collects from you and/or processes. You acknowledge and agree that in the event that such independent third party company experiences a data breach that compromises or otherwise affects your Personal Financial Information, Making Fun shall in no way be responsible or liable to you for such breach. You should contact the applicable independent third party company regarding any such data breach.

**4\. USE AND DISCLOSURE**

_Information Made Public Through Use of the Making Fun Services_

Public Site Content is always publicly available to everyone, including other users, advertisers, search engines, third-party application developers and anyone else with access to the Making Fun Services.

In addition, Making Fun may make your Third-Party Account Information publicly available in accordance with the policies of the third party service from which it was obtained.

_Making Fun’s Use and Disclosure of Information_

We only share your non-public personal information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe sharing is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy.

We use the information we collect from and about users for the following purposes:

**To provide and manage the Making Fun Services**.  We use the information we collect from and about users to provide the Making Fun Services and features to you, which may include to measure and improve those services and features, to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content, advertising and marketing messages, to allow you to participate in online games, contests or promotions, to provide you with customer support, and to respond to inquiries.  We may use aggregated, anonymous data about use of and activity on the Making Fun Services to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

**To allow third-party service providers to assist us in providing and managing the Making Fun Services.**  Making Fun may make your non-public personal information available to certain third-party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the Making Fun Services by, for example: developing or supporting products and features; conducting email marketing on our behalf; processing payments; administering message boards; fulfilling orders; processing data or statistics; or assisting with the administration, judging and prize fulfillment aspects of contests, promotions and sweepstakes. These outside service providers are required to protect non-public personal information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific service they are providing to the Making Fun Services.

**To contact you.**  Making Fun may periodically send promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or notifications related to the Making Fun Services to the email address you provided to us at registration or subscription to a Making Fun Service.  If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from Making Fun, you can follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of as long as you are a member, such as notifications of changes to the Making Fun Services or policies.

**To deliver relevant advertising.  **We may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of the Making Fun Services through cookies and other technologies, to assist us in delivering you relevant ads when you visit the Making Fun Services.  We may work with third-party advertising networks, advertisers and sponsored offer providers who help deliver these ads to you.  We do not share your non-public personal information with these third parties, but we may share anonymized or aggregated information with them to improve the relevancy of the ads you see on the Making Fun Services. As noted above, these third-party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests.  To find out more about third-party online advertising and to opt out of this type of advertising, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Making Fun also shares non-personally identifiable demographic and interest information associated with your account with third-party advertising networks to assist them in delivering relevant ads on Making Fun.

**To protect the rights of  Making Fun and our users. **There may be instances when Making Fun may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where Making Fun has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of Making Fun, our Affiliated Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of users of the Making Fun Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process.  We may retain backup information related to your use of the Making Fun Services on our servers for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies.

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.  **If Making Fun sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, Making Fun may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

**5\. SECURITY**

Making Fun uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard user information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification.

**6\. USER CONTROL AND ACCOUNT CANCELLATION**

To access, correct, cancel, or update your account information, login to your account and go to the account setting. In some cases, in order to cancel your account, you may have to email Making Fun’s customer service at [help@makingfun.com](mailto:help@makingfun.com). Remember that even after you cancel your account, copies of some information from your account may remain viewable in some circumstances – where, for example, you have shared information on the Making Fun Services or with a third-party application or website.  We may also retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after cancelation for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies.  Because of the nature of caching technology, your account may not be instantly inaccessible to others, and we may not be able to remove your content or there may be a delay in the removal of the content from elsewhere on the Internet, for example, from search engines.

**7\. CONTACT US**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Making Fun at:

Email: [privacy@makingfun.com](mailto:privacy@makingfun.com)

Mail:  
Making Fun, Inc  
Attn: Legal Department  
4096 Piedmont Avenue, Suite 944  
Oakland, CA 94611
